export default {
  id: 'low_1006_2_2b',
  name: '상용한자(2학년-2/한자찾기)',
  data: [,
    { question: '독:う(る)、う(れる)/음:ばい', answer: ['売'] },
    { question: '독:か(う)/음:ばい', answer: ['買'] },
    { question: '독:かど/음:もん', answer: ['門'] },
    { question: '독:と/음:こ', answer: ['戸'] },
    { question: '독:い(く)、ゆ(く)、おこな(う)/음:こう、ぎょう、[あん]', answer: ['行'] },
    { question: '독:く(る)、きた(る)、きた(す)/음:らい', answer: ['来'] },
    { question: '독:ある(く)、あゆ(む)/음:ほ、ぶ、[ふ]', answer: ['歩'] },
    { question: '독:はし(る)/음:そう', answer: ['走'] },
    { question: '독:と(まる)、と(める)/음:し', answer: ['止'] },
    { question: '독:かた/음:ほう', answer: ['方'] },
    { question: '독:かど、つの/음:かく', answer: ['角'] },
    { question: '독:いち/음:し', answer: ['市'] },
    { question: '독:ば/음:じょう', answer: ['場'] },
    { question: '독:こころ/음:しん', answer: ['心'] },
    { question: '독:からだ/음:たい、てい', answer: ['体'] },
    { question: '독:あたま、かしら/음:とう、ず、[と]', answer: ['頭'] },
    { question: '독:くび/음:しゅ', answer: ['首'] },
    { question: '독:かお/음:がん', answer: ['顔'] },
    { question: '독:いろ/음:しょく、しき', answer: ['色'] },
    { question: '독:は、はね、[わ]/음:う', answer: ['羽'] },
    { question: '독:け/음:もう', answer: ['毛'] },
    { question: '독:まる、まる(い)、まる(める)/음:がん', answer: ['丸'] },
    { question: '독:かた、かたち/음:けい、ぎょう', answer: ['形'] },
    { question: '독:かたな/음:とう', answer: ['刀'] },
    { question: '독:みせ/음:てん', answer: ['店'] },
    { question: '독:なが(い)/음:ちょう', answer: ['長'] },
    { question: '독:もち(いる)/음:よう', answer: ['用'] },
    { question: '독:재주/음:さい', answer: ['才'] },
    { question: '독:과목/음:か', answer: ['科'] },
    { question: '독:こた(える)、こた(え)/음:とう', answer: ['答'] },
    { question: '독:ひ(く)、ひ(ける)/음:いん', answer: ['引'] },
    { question: '독:줄/음:せん', answer: ['線'] },
    { question: '독:ゆみ/음:きゅう', answer: ['弓'] },
    { question: '독:や/음:し', answer: ['矢'] },
    { question: '독:물 끓는 김/음:き', answer: ['汽'] },
    { question: '독:ふね、[ふな]/음:せん', answer: ['船'] },
    { question: '독:토대/별/음:だい、たい', answer: ['台'] },
    { question: '독:ひか(る)、ひかり/음:こう', answer: ['光'] },
    { question: '독:かみ/음:し', answer: ['紙'] },
    { question: '독:낮/음:ご', answer: ['午'] },
    { question: '독:もと/음:げん、がん', answer: ['元'] },
    { question: '독:ひろ(い)、ひろ(まる)、ひろ(める)、ひろ(がる)、ひろ(げる)/음:こう', answer: ['広'] },
    { question: '독:ふと(い)、ふと(る)/음:た、たい', answer: ['太'] },
    { question: '독:いけ/음:ち', answer: ['池'] },
    { question: '독:たに/음:こく', answer: ['谷'] },
    { question: '독:いわ/음:がん', answer: ['岩'] },
    { question: '독:ほし/음:せい、[しょう]', answer: ['星'] },
    { question: '독:かぜ、かざ/음:ふう、[ふ]', answer: ['風'] },
    { question: '독:うみ/음:かい', answer: ['海'] },
    { question: '독:たか(い)、たか、たか(まる)、たか(める)/음:こう', answer: ['高'] },
    { question: '독:はら/음:げん', answer: ['原'] },
    { question: '독:ゆき/음:せつ', answer: ['雪'] },
    { question: '독:の/음:や', answer: ['野'] },
    { question: '독:き、[こ]/음:おう、こう', answer: ['黄'] },
    { question: '독:くろ、くろ(い)/음:こく', answer: ['黒'] },
    { question: '독:くも/음:うん', answer: ['雲'] },
    { question: '독:땅/음:ち、じ', answer: ['地'] },
    { question: '독:はか(る)/음:ず、と', answer: ['図'] },
    { question: '독:번개/음:でん', answer: ['電'] },
    { question: '독:はな(す)、はなし/음:わ', answer: ['話'] },
    { question: '독:くに/음:こく', answer: ['国'] },
    { question: '독:いえ、や/음:か、け', answer: ['家'] },
    { question: '독:おも(う)/음:し', answer: ['思'] },
    { question: '독:かんが(える)/음:こう', answer: ['考'] },
    { question: '독:살/음:かつ', answer: ['活'] },
    { question: '독:き(る)、き(れる)/음:せつ、[さい]', answer: ['切'] },
    { question: '독:あ(う)、あ(わす)、あ(わせる)/음:ごう、がっ、[かっ]', answer: ['合'] },
    { question: '독:おな(じ)/음:どう', answer: ['同'] },
    { question: '독:まわ(る)、まわ(す)/음:かい、[え]', answer: ['回'] },
    { question: '독:かえ(る)、かえ(す)/음:き', answer: ['帰'] },
    { question: '독:なに、[なん]/음:か', answer: ['何'] },
    { question: '독:あ(かり)、あか(るい)、あか(るむ)、あか(らむ)、あき(らか)、あ(ける)、あ(く)、あ(くる)、あ(かす)/음:めい、みょう', answer: ['明'] },
    { question: '독:あ(たる)、あ(てる)/음:とう', answer: ['当'] },
    { question: '독:ただ(ちに)、なお(す)、なお(る)/음:ちょく、じき', answer: ['直'] },
    { question: '독:あいだ、ま/음:かん、けん', answer: ['間'] },
    { question: '독:다스릴/음:り', answer: ['理'] },
    { question: '독:とお(る)、とお(す)、かよ(う)/음:つう、[つ]', answer: ['通'] },
    { question: '독:し(る)/음:ち', answer: ['知'] },
    { question: '독:は(れる)、は(らす)/음:せい', answer: ['晴'] },
    { question: '독:ほそ(い)、ほそ(る)、こま(か)、こま(かい)/음:さい', answer: ['細'] }
  ]
}
